https://stanfordhealthcare.org/about-us/legal-disclaimer.html

Email
Notice:
Users may be experiencing issues with displaying some pages on stanfordhealthcare.org. We are working closely with our technical teams to resolve the issue as quickly as possible. Thank you for your patience.
COVID-19 Updates:      What We're Doing to Keep You Safe »      COVID-19 Resources »       Updated Visitor Policy »
Menu
Search
Menu
Search
Doctors, Clinics & Locations, Conditions & Treatments
Patients & Visitors
MyHealth
Billing
Contact Us
View All Information for Patients & Visitors »
We are available to assist you 24/7.
650-498-3333
GuestServices@stanfordhealthcare.org
View the changes to our visitor policy »
View information for Guest Services »
New to MyHealth?
Manage Your Care From Anywhere.
Access your health information from any device with MyHealth.  You can message your clinic, view lab results, schedule an appointment, and pay your bill.
ALREADY HAVE AN ACCESS CODE?
Activate Account
DON'T HAVE AN ACCESS CODE?
Create a New Account
NEED MORE DETAILS?
Learn More about MyHealth »
MyHealth for Mobile
Get the iPhone MyHealth app »
Get the Android MyHealth app »
WELCOME BACK
Forgot Username or Password?
Need Help?
Clear
About Us: Legal Disclaimer
About
About
Legal Notices and Disclaimers
Terms and Conditions of Use
Welcome to the Stanford Health Care's Web Site (the "Site"). Please read the following Terms and Conditions of Use ("Terms") carefully before using the Site. It governs your relationship with Stanford Health Care regarding your use of the Site.
You should not substitute information on the Stanford Health Care Web site for professional advice.
This Web site provides general educational information. This information is not provided in the course of a professional relationship between a health care provider and a patient. It is not intended to be, and should not be used as, a substitute for medical treatment by a health care professional.
Stanford Health Care is not making a diagnosis of your condition or a recommendation about the course of treatment for your particular circumstances through the use of this Web site. You should not assume that information on a particular topic on the site is complete or up-to-date. You should never disregard or delay seeking medical advice because of what you have read on this Web site.
Your Permission to use the Stanford Health Care Web site.
Stanford Health Care give you limited personal permission to use the Web site. Your permission to use the Web site is limited in a number of ways. For example, the only use for which you may use, download, or print material contained on this Site is for internal non-profit research purposes. Any commercial use, such as selling content, creating course packs, or posting information on another Web site, is prohibited. You also may not:
frame all or part of the Web site.
change or delete any proprietary notices from materials downloaded or printed out from the Web site.
systemically download or print materials from the Web site.
transmit or provide any data from the Web site to a third party.
use the Web site in a manner contrary to any applicable law.
Your permission terminates immediately, without any further action by Stanford Health Care, if you breach these Terms. You may not transfer or assign your permission to any other party.
Stanford Health Care is the owner or licensee of all rights in the Web site, its content, software, and services. You have no right to such content, software or services if not expressly granted in this Agreement. "Stanford Health Care" and the logos or other proprietary marks of Stanford Health Care's licensors and partners are trademarks of Stanford Health Care or its licensors and partners. No right, title or interest in those trademarks is granted you in this Agreement.
The Site is Provided "As Is."
SERVICES PROVIDED THROUGH AND INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THE SITE ARE PROVIDED AS IS AND AS AVAILABLE. STANFORD HEALTH CARE MAKES NO, AND HEREBY DISCLAIMS ANY, WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF TITLE, NONINFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR USE OR PURPOSE. FURTHER, STANFORD HEALTH CARE DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTY THAT THE SITE WILL BE AVAILABLE AT ALL TIMES OR WILL OPERATE WITHOUT INTERRUPTION OR ERROR. STANFORD HEALTH CARE MAKES NO WARRANTY AS TO THE RELIABILITY, ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, USEFULNESS, ADEQUACY, COMPLETENESS OR SUITABILITY OF THE SERVICES OR INFORMATION PROVIDED THROUGH THE SITE.
You Alone are Responsible for Your Use of the Site.
You agree to be solely responsible for your use of this Web site.
STANFORD HEALTH CARE, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, AND INFORMATION PROVIDERS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES YOU MAY SUFFER OR CAUSE THROUGH YOUR USE OF THE SITE EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
STANFORD HEALTH CARE, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, AND INFORMATION PROVIDERS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF YOUR USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SITE.
THESE LIMITATIONS SHALL APPLY WHETHER THE ASSERTED LIABILITY OR DAMAGES ARE BASED IN CONTRACT (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, BREACH OF WARRANTY), TORT (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, NEGLIGENCE) OR ANY OTHER LEGAL OR EQUITABLE GROUNDS.
You agree to indemnify and hold Stanford Health Care harmless for any claims, losses or damages, including attorneys fees, resulting from your breach of these terms or use of this Web site.
Stanford Health Care is Not Responsible for Any Links To or From Other Sites.
This Web site may contain links to other Web sites, and other Web sites may provide links to this Site. These links are provided for your convenience only. Stanford Health Care does not control these other sites and assumes no liability or responsibility for them, including any content or services provided to you by such sites. You should not consider any link to or from another site as an endorsement of that site by Stanford Health Care unless Stanford Health Care expressly states so. Stanford Sites utilize YouTube API Services. Links to the applicable Terms of Service and Privacy Policies are listed below.
Terms of Service of YouTube
Privacy Policy of Google
Privacy policy of Instagram
Privacy policy of Twitter
Privacy policy of Facebook
Privacy policy of LinkedIn
Privacy policy of Foresee
Privacy policy of Liveperson
Browser Cookies And Web Beacons
We may use browser "cookies” or web beacons to make our sites and services more useful to you. Browser cookies are small data files placed on the computer hard drives of users of our web and mobile apps.   Cookies help us to tailor our apps to be more helpful and efficient for you. The cookie consists of a unique identifier that does not contain information about you or your health history. We use two types of cookies:
Session cookies help customize your experience on our site, by maintaining your signed-on status as you navigate through, and tracking your "click path” through our pages or screens. Session cookies are temporary, and expire after the session ends and you close your browser or app.
Persistent cookies remain on your hard drive after you've exited from our website. If you've given us permission to send you information about our services, we may place a persistent cookie on your hard drive that will let us know when you come back to visit our site.
We may also use cookies in combination with a "Web beacon". Web beacons are small graphic files that are also used to understand how you are using the site.
When you access the Sites through a mobile device or browser, Stanford Health Care may utilize a feature that accesses, collects, monitors and/or remotely stores “location data,” which may include GPS coordinates (longitude and latitude) or other location information, and may share such data with third-parties such as Google. You may opt-in or opt-out of sharing location data from your computer by through the settings on your browser or mobile device.
You may have software on your computer that will allow you to decline or deactivate cookies and beacons. If you do so, some features of the Websites or the App may not work properly for you. For instructions on how to remove cookies from your hard drive, go to your browser's website for detailed instructions. In addition, further information regarding cookies may be available on other websites or from your Internet service provider.
You Agree that Stanford Health Care May Share Certain Information About You.
You agree that, should you elect to supply it, Stanford Health Care may use your name, e-mail address, physical address, or other data to communicate with you. You may request to have this information modified or deleted from our records. Stanford Health Care Site may use this information as necessary to enforce these Terms. Stanford Health Care will not sell this information to any other party.
This Agreement is Governed by California Law.
This Agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California, United States of America, as such laws would apply to a contract fully negotiated, entered into, and performed in that state.
You Agree to Arbitrate Any Dispute Between Us.
You agree that any dispute, controversy or claim arising out of or related to these Terms or your use of the Site will be resolved and settled through arbitration administered by the American Arbitration Association and conducted in Santa Clara, California, United States of America. Judgment on any award rendered by the arbitrator may be entered in any court of competent jurisdiction.
Any Action Against Stanford Health Care Must be Brought in California.
You agree that the state or federal courts located in or serving Santa Clara County, California, United States of America, shall have exclusive jurisdiction and venue over any action arising out of or relating to these Terms or your use of the Site. You waive any claim that a court located in or serving Santa Clara County, California, lacks personal jurisdiction over you, is an improper venue, or is an inconvenient forum.
Other Miscellaneous Provisions.
These Terms constitute the entire and only understanding between you and Stanford Health Care regarding your use of this Web site. No modification or attempted modification of these Terms by you shall be binding on Stanford Health Care unless made in writing and physically signed by an authorized representative of Stanford Health Care. Stanford Health Care may modify these Terms at any time.
Notices sent to you by Stanford Health Care in connection with these Terms or your use of the Site may be delivered to you by electronic mail, a general notice on the Site, or by written communication delivered by first class U. S. mail. You may give notice to Stanford Health Care at any time by letter delivered by first class postage prepaid U. S. mail or overnight courier to the following address:
Stanford Health Care
Attention: Web Center
300 Pasteur Drive
Palo Alto, CA 94304-5547
These Terms are severable to the extent any term is deemed invalid, illegal or unenforceable.
Stanford Health Care's failure to enforce any provision of these Terms shall not be deemed a waiver of that or any other provision of these Terms.
Your use and continued use of the Stanford Health Care's Site reflects your agreement to these Terms and any modifications of these Terms made by the Stanford Health Care.
Newsroom
Careers
Volunteering
Vendors
University HealthCare Alliance
Stanford Health Care – ValleyCare
Stanford Medicine
Stanford Children's Health
|   Notice of Nondiscrimination     ©2020 Stanford Health Care. All Rights Reserved
